Biographical files (UCLA University Archives Reference Collection). 1882- UARC.0745
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Biographical Files., 1882-; Series 1.
  - Snyder, Allegra Fuller.
    UCLA Faculty Dance Department: dean, UCLA School of the Arts; research in dance ethnology.
  - Sokolnikoff, Ivan Stephan., 1 folder
    UCLA mathematics professor 1946 - 1965.
  - Soll, Sidney., b.1911 - d.2008
  - Solmon, Lewis C., d.2007
    UCLA Education Professor; Dean, UCLA Graduate School of Education (1985-1991).
  - Solomon, Robert C.
  - Solorio, Rosa.
  - Sorenson, Olav J., b. 1969.
  - Sork, Victoria.
  - Soto, Raymond.
  - Spaulding, William Henry., 1880 May 4 - 1966 October
    William H. (Bill) Spaulding served as UCLA football coach from 1925-1938; in 1938 Spaulding retired from coaching to become the UCLA athletic director.
  - Speroni, Carmela Corica.
    Served as President of the UCLA Art Council.
  - Speroni, Charles., b.1911-d.1984
    Dean, College of Fine Arts (1968-1979).
  - Speyer, Jason L.
  - Spicer, Leslie.
  - Sproul, Ida Amelia Wittschen., b.1891
  - Sproul, Robert Gordon.
    President of the University of California.
    Includes fifteen (15) letters, 1942-1963, from Robert G. Sproul to Rosalie Trope Lewis (UCLA 1942).
  - St.John, Kristen.
  - Starkie, Walter Fitzwilliam., b.1894 August 9 - d.1976 November 2
    UCLA Professor, Spanish; Center for the Study of Comparative Folklore and Mythology.
  - Staton, Paul.
  - Stein, Jules Ceasar., b.1896-
  - Steiner, George A., b. 1912.
  - Steinitz, Kate Traumann., b.1889 - c.1975
    In 1941 Steinmetz became the Librarian for Elmer Belt's collection of Leonardo da Vinci. The Elmer Belt Library of Vinciana was donated to the UCLA Library by Belt in 1961.
  - Stevenson, Brenda.
  - Stevenson, Robert M.
    UCLA Professor of Musicology, Emeritus.
  - Stoutmeyer, Vernon T., b.1905 January 9
    UCLA Professor of Botany (College of Agriculture); Professor of Agricultural Sciences; Associate Director of the California Agriculture Experiment Station. Stoutmeyer retired from UCLA in 1972.
  - Stoutmeyer, Vernon T., b.1905 january 9
  - Stowell, Timothy.
  - Straus, Ernst Gabor., b. 1922 - d. 1983
    Member of the UCLA Department of Math faculty from 1948 to 1983.
  - Strode, Woodrow Wilson Woolwine "Woody" (UCLA attended 1936/37-1939/40)., b.1914 July 25 - d.1994 December 31
    UCLA football player and film actor.
  - Strong, Gary E.
    UCLA University Librarian (2003 September - 2012 December).
  - Suchard, Marc
  - Sumner, Anne (UCLA 1926)., b.1904 July - d.2008 February 9
  - Sundquist, Eric J.
  - Sussman, Eric.
  - Svenson, Elwin Victor., b.1926 February 12
    UCLA Vice Chancellor for Institutional Relations (appointed 1975 July).
  - Szego, Claire (Clara) M., b.1916
    UCLA faculty Biology Department (Division of Molecular, Cell and Developmental Biology).
  - Takasugi Mitsuo., b.1928 - d.2008
  - Tamanoi, Mariko.
  - Tangherlini, Timothy.
  - Tannenbaum, Robert., b. 1915 - d. 2003.
  - Taylor, Angus Ellis., d.1911-d.1999
    UCLA faculty, Mathematics Department; chairman of the University of California Academic Senate (1964); University of California vice president of Academic Affairs (appointed 1965); Chancellor of UC Santa Cruz (1976-1977). Includes: three (3) unpublished autobiographical chapters pertaining to Taylor's years at UCLA; eulogy for Mary Kathleen Lapham Taylor (b.1910 - d.1982), wife of Angus E. Taylor.
  - Thomas, Dominic.
  - Thomas, Evalyn Ann., b.1870 - d.1950
    Los Angeles State Normal School faculty in Reading; UCLA faculty in English. Produced and directed numerous student productions of Greek tragedy from c.1916 to 1938.
  - Thompson, Harland (Hal) B.
  - Thornberg, Christopher.
  - Tietze, Andreas.
  - Titcomb, Lillian Ray., b.1873-d.1974
    UCLA physician for women, 1919-1942; B.A. Stanford University, 1897; M.A. Stanford University, 1901; M.D. Johns Hopkins University, 1908.
  - Titman, Sheridan D., b. 1954.
  - Traweek, Sharon.
  - Trope Lewis, Rosalee Diane (UCLA 1942).
    Rosalee Diane Trope was college poet laureate of California. SEE ALSO: Lewis, Benjamin G.; Sproul, Robert Gordon.
  - Tucker, Alan M.
  - Turner, Ralph H.
    UCLA faculty, Sociology Department.
  - Turner, Roderick, d.2004
  - Tyler, Louise L., d.2004
  - Valentine, William Newton., b.1917 September 29
  - Van Valkenburgh, Blaire.
  - Vermeil, Dick., b.1936 October 30
    Dick Vermeil served as a UCLA assistant football coach in 1970 and as UCLA's head football coach during the 1974 and 1975 seasons.
  - Villaraigosa, Antonio.
  - Voge, Marietta.
    UCLA Professor of Microbiology and Immunology.
  - von Grunebaum, Gustave Edmund., b.1909-d.1972
    Includes: 'The real significance of Iran's 2,500-year anniversary,' 1971 November (typescript).
    UCLA Professor of History and Director, Near Eastern Center.
  - Vosper, Robert Gordon., b.1913 - d.1994
  - Vroon, Ronald.
  - Vryonis, Speros.
  - Wade, Ronald Ellis.
    Includes letters and memos (photocopies) regarding the 1976 theft of materials from the UCLA Dept. of Special Collections.
    Wade pleaded guilty on 1976 August 31 to having stolen 150+ historical documents and letters from the UCLA Department of Special Collections. The trial was held in the Los Angeles County Superior Court before Judge Pearce Young.
  - Ward, Donald J., b.1930 - d.2004
  - Warren, Stafford Leak., b.1896 - d.1981
    Includes audio recording of Stafford L. Warren's memorial service (1981 October 2).
    First dean of UCLA School of Medicine (1947-1963).
  - Washington, A. Eugene.
  - Washington, Kenneth "Kenny" Stanley (UCLA 1941)., b.1918 August 31 - d.1971 June 24
    UCLA football player; was the first UCLA football player to be designated a consensus All-American; was voted UCLA football team's MVP [most valuable player] in 1939.
  - Watstein, Sarah.
    UCLA Library Associate University Librarian for Research and Instructional Services (2005 March 28).
  - Wazzan, A. R. (Ahmed Rassem) Frank., b.1935 October 17
  - Webster, Gordon.
  - Weinreich, Max.
    Max Weinreich, visiting UCLA professor who taught courses in Yiddish folk literature and Yiddish linguistics (Summer 1948), UCLA Dept. of German; research director of YIVO, Yiddish Scientific Institute of New York City.
  - Wells, Dorothy Viola., b.1916 - d.2004
  - Werner, Gloria S.
    Includes audio interview (1983 October 18).
    UCLA University Librarian, 1990 June-2002 June.
  - Werner, Newton Davis., b.1934 June 18 - d.2000 October 3
  - Weston, J. Frederick., b. 1916 - d. 2009.
  - West, Louis Jolyon, M.D., b.1924 October 6 - d.1999 January 2
    Louis Jolyon "Jolly" West, chair of the UCLA Department of Behavioral Sciences and director of the UCLA Neuropsychiatric Institute (NPI), 1969-1988.
    Includes: Neuropsychiatric Grand Rounds Tribute to Louis Jolyon West, 1999 March 2 (video tape recording - two VHS cassettes).
  - White, Kari Windingstad.
  - White, Kathryn Perdew.
  - Whitman, Alfred Russell., b.1882 - d.1940
  - Whybrow, Peter C.
  - Wight, Frederic S., b.1902 June 1 - d.
    UCLA Professor of Art, Director of the [Art] Galleries (1953-1972).
  - Wildman, Samuel Goodnow.
  - Williams, Harold M., b. 1928.
  - Williams, Robert M., b. 1913 - d. 2001.
    Williams was founder and director of the UCLA Business Forecasting Project from 1952-1981; Business Forecasting Project later renamed Anderson Forecast.
  - Willison, Bruce G.
  - Wilson, Charles Z., Jr.
    UCLA Assistant Vice Chancellor, Education Planning (1968-1970); UCLA Vice Chancellor Academic Programs (1970-1984).
  - Wilson, James Q., b. 1931 - d. 2012.
  - Wilson, Howard E.
    Dean, UCLA School of Education, 1955 July.
  - Wilson, Rayma Bess (UCLA 1932).
    Participated in 1928 Olympics (track) and held world's record for 800 meter event.
  - Winstein, Saul., d.1969
    UCLA Professor of Chemistry, 1941-1969.
  - With, Karl Eberhard., b.1891 - d.1980
    UCLA Professor, Department of Art (Art History).
  - Witte, Owen N.
    UCLA Distinguished Profession Microbiology, Immunology adn Molecular Genetics; UCLA Faculty Research Lecturer (2007 November 8).
  - Wolfe, Nathan.
    UCLA Professor, Epidemiology.
  - Wolfenstein, Eugene Victor., b. 1940 July 9 - d.2010 December 15
    UCLA faculty, Political Science and psychoanalyst.
  - Wortham, Thomas.
    UCLA Professor, English.
  - Wright, Edward.
  - Xi, Jianzhong.
  - Yaghi, Omar
  - Yamazaki, James N.
    Clinical Professor in Pediatrics.
  - Yang, Chuan-Kwang (CK), b. 1933 - d.2007
  - Yang, Daniel C.H.
  - Young, Charles Edward., b.1931 December 30 -
    UCLA Chancellor (1968 September 1 to 1997 June 30).
  - Young, Colin., b.1927-
    UCLA Professor Theater Arts (1957-1970); head of UCLA Motion Picture Division (1964-1965); Theater Arts department chair (1965-1970).
  - Young, Kevin.
  - Young, Sue K., b.1932 - d.2001
    Wife of UCLA Chancellor Charles E. Young.
  - Zhong, Xiaolin.
  - Zide, Harry A., b.1909 - d.2010
- Biographical Files - Photographs., 1882-; Series 2.
  - Abdul-Jabbar, Kareem [Ferdinand Lewis Alcindor] (UCLA 1969).
  - Aboody, David.
  - Ackerman, Page., b.1912 June 30 - d.2006 February 28
  - Ackerman, William C.
  - Adams, Captain.
  - Adams, Forrest H.
    UCLA Pediatric Cardiology Professor.
  - Adderley, Julian "Cannonball."
    Includes publicity photograph relating to UCLA's Julian "Cannonball" Adderley Benefit Concert.
  - Adizes, Ichak., b. 1937.
  - Adsit, Ted.
  - Agajanian, Larry., 1967
    Football men
  - Ahmadi, Reza H.
  - Alam El Din, Ibrahim.
  - Allen, Bennet.
  - Allen, Edward.
  - Allen, Leroy.
  - Allen, M.G.
  - Allen, Raymond B.
    Includes: Chancellor Allen's office staff Christmas Party (1952, 1953).
  - Altenburg, Kurt., 1963-1964
  - Altman, Pat.
  - Andersen, Theodore A., b. 1920.
  - Anderson, Diana W.
  - Anderson, John E., b. 1917 - d. 2011.
  - Anderson, Laura.
  - Andrews, Robert B.
  - Andrusyshyn, Zenon., 1967
  - Appleman, David.
  - Arlt, Gustav O.
  - Arrillaga, Randy.
    UCLA men's basketball team member: 1980, 1981, 1982, 1983.
  - Ashbaugh, James Graham.
  - Ashe, Arthur (UCLA 1965).
    Includes images of Ashe on UCLA varsity tennis team.
  - Ashford, Evelyn.
    Participated in the 1984 Olympics (track: 100 and 400 meters).
  - Atsatt, Sara Rodgers.
  - Backhouse, Judith.
  - Bailey, Kenneth P. (UCLA Ph.D. 1938)
  - Bair, J.A.
  - Baisden, Richard N.
  - Baker, Marjorie.
  - Baldwin, [ ? ].
  - Ball, Gordon.
  - Ballou, Mike., 1967
  - Barber, Lloyd Delos.
    Includes an image of the interior of Delos' Westwood campus construction office.
    Appointed by the University of California Regents as the supervising architect (1926-1935) during the construction of UCLA's Westwood campus.
  - Barja, Cesar.
  - Barker, M.J.
  - Barker, Wiley F.
    UCLA Clinical Professor of Surgery.
  - Barlow, Bob.
  - Barnes, Ralph., b. 1900 - d. 1984.
  - Bartlett, Emely.
  - Baugh, Ruth.
  - Beban, Gary.
  - Beban, Gary.
  - Beck, Paul J., b. 1951.
  - Beebe, Elinor Lee.
  - Beerman, Leonard I.
  - Bell, Clifford.
  - Bellamy, A.
  - Benartzi, Shromo.
  - Bennett, Charles [B.?].
  - Bennett, Charles [F., Jr.?].
  - Bennett, Charles.
  - Beranek, William.
  - Bergstrom, Karen.
  - Bernardo, Antonio.
  - Bialoglawsky, Joseph.
  - Bibby, Henry.
    UCLA men's basketball team member: 1970, 1971, 1972.
  - Bigelow, [ ? ].
  - Bikhehandani, Sushil.
  - Billington, Barry.
  - Bjork, David K.
  - Blacet, F.E.
  - Blakey, Roy.
  - Blanchard, Frederick Thomas.
  - Blanco De Neve, Jose M.
  - Blok, Jack.
  - Boelter, L.M.K. [Llewelyn Michael Kraus].
  - Boggert, Charles Mitchill.
  - Boje, David M., b. 1947.
  - Bolden, Bill., n.d.
  - Bolton, Laura.
  - Bontemps, Arna.
  - Boonsaith, Boonan.
  - Booth, Bradford A.
  - Bounet, Paul.
  - Bovard, John F.
  - Bowen, Brent.
  - Bowman, Donald.
  - Boyd, Barbara.
  - Boyer, Paul D.
  - Bradbury, Ray.
  - Bradford, Leland.
  - Bradley, Omar. [U.S. General]
    SEE: Commencement, 1948 (Photograph Collection)
  - Bradley, Thomas "Tom." (UCLA attended 1937-1940)
    Includes image of Tom Bradley Admininstrative Files Project Team,1997 March (UCLA Library Dept. of Special Collections).
  - Brainerd, [ ? ].
  - Bratton, Truman R.
  - Breck, [ ? ].
  - Brennan, Michael J., b. 1942.
  - Brenner, Robert, b.1943
    UCLA faculty, History (U.S. Economic Historian).
  - Breslow, Lester.
    UCLA Professor and Dean, School of Public Health.
  - Broesamle, William H., b. 1942.
  - Brown, Edmund G. ("Pat").
  - Brown, Joe E.
  - Brown, William F.
  - Brownwell, Keith W.
  - Bruman, Henry.
  - Bryan, Elizabeth.
  - Buchannan, Frances.
  - Buchele, [ ? ].
  - Buchele, [ ? ].
  - Buckley, John W., b. 1934 - d. 2012.
  - Bucklin, Randolph E.
  - Buell, L.M.
  - Buettner, Konrad.
  - Buffa, Elwood S., b. 1923 - d. 2005.
  - Bugental, Robert.
  - Bunche, John.
  - Bunche, Ralph Johnson. (UCLA 1927), b.1904 - d.1971
  - Bunting, Allison.
  - Burleson, G.L.
  - Burnett, Carol. (attended UCLA 1951-1954), b.1933 April 26
  - Burns, E. Bradford., b.1932 August 28 - d.1995 December 19
    UCLA Professor, History.
  - Burns, Leland S.
  - Burns, Robert I., S.J., b.1921 August 16 - d.2008 November 22
  - Bush, Jim., n.d.
    Track and Field men
  - Bynum, Lindley.
  - Caldwell, Robert.
  - Cameron, Paul., n.d.
  - Campbell, Lily Bess.
  - Campbell, Robert.
  - Campbell, William Wallace.
  - Campbell, William Wallace., 1862-1938
    Tenth (10th) University of California President, 1923-1930.
  - Caplan, Jerry.
  - Carmon, [ ? ].
  - Carpenter, Charles M.
    UCLA Professor of Infectious Diseases; first chairman of the Dept. of Infectious Diseases.
  - Carrabino, Joseph., b. 1923 - d. 2007.
  - Cassady, Ralph Jr., b. 1900 - d. 1978.
  - Castagna, Edwin.
  - Cates, Gilbert., b.1934 - d.2011
  - Caughey, John Walton.
    UCLA Professor History Department.
  - Chaix, Alfred V.
  - Champion, Cornell., 1964
  - Chase, Joseph.
  - Cheadle, Vernon I.
  - Chen, Peter Pin-Shan., b. 1947.
  - Chowdhry, Bhagwan.
  - Christian, Peggy.
  - Christianson, Bob., n.d.
  - Churchill, [ ? ].
  - Claman, Alan., 1966
  - Clark, James V.
  - Cloonan, Michele Valerie.
    UCLA Professor of Information Studies.
  - Coldren, Fanny.
  - Collins, Katherine Estelle.
  - Coney, Donald.
  - Connery, Maurice.
  - Consales, Judy.
  - Cooper, Lee G., b. 1944.
  - Copenhaver, Brian.
  - Corbett, Charles.
  - Corday, Eliot.
  - Corley, J.H.
  - Cornell, Bradford., b. 1947.
  - Cornell, Ralph D.
  - Cowles, Ray.
  - Cram, Donald J.
  - Crandall, Barbara.
  - Crandell [Crandall], Alice "Ma" Weller.
  - Crocker, William Henry.
  - Croft, Robert.
  - Cromwell, Leslie.
  - Crossland, James.
  - Crum, Denny., n.d.
    Basketball men
  - Crummett, [ ? ].
  - Crump, Nadine.
  - Cubberly, Hazel.
  - Culbert, Samuel A.
  - Cunningham, Gary., n.d.
  - Cunningham, Thomas J.
  - Cureton, Mickey., n.d.
  - Currie, [ ? ].
  - Currim, Imran S., b. 1951.
  - Curtis, Philip C.
  - Dabagh, Thomas Suren., b.1903 February 12
  - Dakan, Arthur.
  - Dalton, Melville.
  - Darby, Michael.
  - Darcus, Roy M.
  - Davis, Angela.
  - Davis, Booker T.
  - Davis, Edna.
    Librarian, William Andrews Clark Memorial Library.
  - Davis, Hiram Logan.
  - Daye, Darren.
  - De Groot, [ ? ].
  - De Silva, Gallay.
  - Deane, Martha.
  - De La Torre, Jose., b. 1943.
  - Denitz, Herm.
  - Dewey, John.
    Includes 1930 March 26 image taken one day prior to the dedication ceremonies of UCLA's Westwood campus (March 27 & 28, 1930).
  - Dhir, Vijay K., b.1943 April 14
  - Diamond, Jared Mason., b.1937 September 10
  - Dick, Hugh G.
  - Dickson, Edward A.
    Includes photograph of: Earl Warren (California Governor), Stafford L. Warren (Dean, UCLA Medical School), and Edward A. Dickson (University of California Regent) at groundbreaking of UCLA Medical Center(?), c.1951.
  - Dill, Hellen C.
  - Dodd, Paul A.
  - Dodson, Leigh Marian.
  - Dolch, A.K.
  - Dole, William.
  - Domiguez, John R.
  - Donahue, Terry.
  - Donahue, Terry., n.d.
    Football men (player 1965-1966, coach 1971-1995)
  - Donnan, Christopher B.
    UCLA Professor of Anthropology; Director of the UCLA Museum of Cultural History.
  - Dorcus, Roy M., d.1965
    Professor of Psychology; Professor of Psychology in the UCLA School of Medicine.
  - Dorsee, Ruth.
  - Downess, C.S.
  - Dracup, Kathleen.
  - Drolet, Aimee.
  - Du Bois, Chartolle.
  - Dudley, George.
  - Duke, C. Martin.
  - Dummit, Dennis., n.d.
  - Dunlap, Knight.
  - Dunn, Max.
  - Durant, Henry.
  - Dutton, W.H.
  - Dyer, James S.
  - Dykstra, Clarence Addison., b.1883-d.1950
  - Eby, Harbey L.
  - Echols, Reggie., 1971
  - Eckbo, Garrett.
  - Edwards, Sebastian.
  - Effenbach, Leah.
  - Eiteman, David K., b. 1930.
  - Ellis, J.W.
  - Emerson, Gladys.
  - Engelke, Marian Elizabeth., b.1921 - d.2009 December 25
  - Erickson, Christopher.
  - Erlenkotter, Donald., b. 1938.
  - Erlichman, John (UCLA 1948).
    Erlichman was a member of the administrative staff for U.S. President Richard M. Nixon. SEE ALSO: Commencement, 1948 (Photograph Collections).
  - Euler, Esther.
  - Ewing, Majl.
  - Falick, Abe.
  - Farmer, Larry.
    UCLA men's basketball team, 1970-1972.
  - Farr, Mel., 1965, n.d.
  - Fearing, Franklin.
  - Fernald, Grace Maxwell.
    UCLA faculty in Psychology. Grace Maxwell Fernald served as director of the Fernald School, formerly known as the Clinic School, from its founding in 1921 until 1946.
  - Fielding, Gordon J.
  - Fields, Kenny.
    UCLA men's basketball team member: 1981, 1982, 1983, 1984.
  - Fielstra, Clarence.
  - Fisher, Raymond.
  - Fisher, S.C.
  - Fite, A.G.
  - Fitzgibbon, Russell H.
  - Flamholtz, Eric., b. 1943.
  - Fleming, Ed.
  - Fletcher, John Gould.
  - Flores, Mike., 1971
  - Fogel, Walter A., b. 1932 - d. 2003.
  - Forman, Mildred.
  - Foster, Rod.
  - Fox, Richard.
  - Frampton, Paul.
  - Francisco, Kent., 1963
  - Frand, Jason L., b. 1942.
  - Frankenbach, Edwin.
  - Frederickson, Hansena.
  - Friedlander, Sheldon K., b.1927 - d.2007
  - Frisbee, Ira N.
  - Geis, George T.
  - Gengerelli, J.A.
  - Geoffrion, Arthur., b. 1937.
  - Gerard, Dora.
  - Gershwin, George.
    Includes photograph of George Gershwin playing "Strike Up the Band" with members of UCLA's Delta Gamma Sorority[?] (1937 February 2).
  - Geske, Robert L.
  - Ghedai, Abebe.
  - Gibling, Dorothy S.
  - Gibson, Arthur C.
  - Gilhousen, Howard C., b.1895 - d.1969
  - Gimbel, Jake.
  - Glazier, Harriet.
  - Glendinning, R.M.
  - Goddard, Vera(?) R.
  - Gold, Marvin H. (UCLA 1937)
  - Goldman, Don.
  - Goldschmidt, Walter.
  - Goldwater, Barry.
  - Golino, Carlo.
  - Gonzalez, Simon.
  - Goodman, Richard A., b. 1939 - d. 2004.
  - Goodrich, Gail., 1963
  - Goodspeed, Edgar J.
  - Goodwin, John Edward.
  - Gordon, Dianne.
  - Goss, Hilton.
  - Graham, Malbone.
  - Granfield, Michael E., b. 1943.
  - Grannis, Lawrence C.
  - Grant, U.S.
  - Graves, Glenn W.
  - Gray, Greta.
  - Gray, Hilda M.
  - Gray, Hugh J., b.1900 Sep 4-d.1981 Feb 13
  - Gray, Hugh.
  - Gray, Stuart.
    UCLA men's basketball team member: 1982, 1983, 1984.
  - Greenberger, Martin.
  - Gregor, Howard.
  - Grenit, A.
  - Grider, Dallas., 1965
  - Grinblatt, Mark S.
  - Griffith, [ ? ].
  - Grunewald, L.
  - Gustafson, Mark., 1967
  - Haar, Charles.
  - Haefner, Harold.
  - Haggerty, Ron.
  - Hahn, Eloise.
  - Hale, Gerry A.
  - Halley, William.
  - Halmo, F.F.
  - Halpern, Steven Joel (UCLA 1973).
  - Hamill, Harold L.
  - Hamilton, Andrew.
  - Hammond, George P.
  - Hand, Wayland.
  - Hannum, Paul.
  - Hanssens, Dominique.
  - Harlow, Neal.
  - Harries, Keith.
  - Harrison, Gilbert (UCLA 1937).
    Includes images of: Hal Levy, Gilbert Harrison, William Okie - founders of The Conference Press - with author William Saroyan (c.1936); Gilbert Harrison and Page Ackerman viewing UCLA Library Gertrude Stein exhibition (1974).
  - Harshberger, Edith.
  - Hartshorn, Elizabeth.
  - Hartsock, Donald.
  - Hassan, Hasson I.
  - Hassenplug, Lulu.
  - Haupt, Arthur W.
  - Hausen, Victor.
  - Hauster, Richard.
  - Hawkins, Alma.
  - Hayn, Carla.
  - Hazen, Bessie Ella.
  - Hazzard, Walt.
  - Hazzard, Walt.
    UCLA men's basketball team member, 1962-1964; UCLA men's basketball coach, 1984/1985 to 1987/1988.
  - Healy, Jack.
  - Hechtman, B.
  - Hedrick, Earle Raymond., b.1897 - d.1943
  - Hefferman, Helen.
  - Heifitz, Jascha.
  - Henderson, John D.
  - Henderson, Scott., 1971
  - Hernandez, Joaquin.
  - Heron, Alexander.
  - Hershey, Mira., d.1930
  - Hestenes, R.
  - Hildemann, William H.
    UCLA faculty, Infectious Diseases; UCLA Professor of Medical Microbiology and Immunology; Director, Dental Research Institute, UCLA School of Dentistry (1972 March).
  - Hirshleifer, David A., b. 1958.
  - Hitch, Charles J.
  - Hodgson, James Day., b. 1915 - d. 2012.
  - Hodgson, Robert W.
  - Hoeber, Ralph C., b. 1898 - d. 1978.
  - Hoffleit, Herbert B.
  - Hoffman, Paul.
  - Hogge, C.W.
  - Hoisch, Al., 1947?
  - Holloway, Chuck., 1956
  - Holton, Karl.
  - Holton, Michael.
  - Holzer, Robert E.
  - Hood, Mantle.
    UCLA faculty in Music, Institute of Ethnomusicology, and Ethnomusicology.
  - Hooker, Evelyn N.
  - Hoover, Louise Brown. (UCLA 1930)
  - Hoover, Thelner. (UCLA 1930)
  - Horgan, Paul., 1964
  - Horn, Andrew Harlis., b.1914 - d.1983
  - Horn, Andrew.
  - Horvath, Ronald.
  - Houser, Frederick.
  - Houston, [ ? ].
  - Hughes, Patricia J., b. 1943 - d. 2007.
  - Humason, L.H.
  - Humphreys, Clara.
  - Hunt, B.M.
  - Hunt, Gary.
  - Hurd, [ ? ].
  - Hussey, Luther.
  - Hustvedt, Sigurd B.
  - Hutchinson, [ ? ].
  - Hutchinson, John E., b. 1921.
  - Huxley, Aldous.
  - Hyde, Edith.
  - Inskeep, Edward Lee.
  - Iturbi, Jose.
  - Izzard, [ ? ].
  - Jackey, David F.
  - Jackson, James R., b. 1924 - d. 2011.
  - Jackson, John B. (UCLA 1927)
  - Jackson, Ralph.
  - Jacoby, Neil H., b. 1909 - d. 1979.
  - Jacoby, Stanford M., b. 1953.
  - Jensen, Thomas Arden.
  - Jessen, Raymond J., b. 1910 - d. 2003.
  - Johnson, [ ? ].
  - Johnson, Kermit., 1971
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines.
    U.S. President; attended 1964 UCLA Charter Day.
  - Johnson, Marques.
  - Johnson, Rafer.
  - Johnson, Ralph P.
  - Jones, Greg., 1967-1968
  - Jones, Marian Anne Bunker (UCLA 1949, M.A. 1954)
  - Kaplan, Abraham.
  - Kaplan, Joseph.
  - Karst, Kenneth L.
  - Keislar, Evan R.
  - Keller, A.D.
  - Kelly, W.P.
  - Kendricks, Marv., 1971
  - Kennedy, George C., b.1920 - d.1980 March 18
  - Kennedy, Mary (Mrs. E. J.)
    UCLA Curator in Fine Arts.
  - Kennel, Charles F.
  - Kerckhoff, William George., b.1856 March 30 - d.1929 February 22
  - Kerr, Clark.
  - Ketteringham, William James.
  - Kichesky, Mrs. Boris
  - Kickert, Ronald.
  - King, Kermit C.
  - King, Martin Luther, Jr.
  - Kinsey, Doug.
  - Kinsey, Edgar Lee.
  - Kinsey, Midge.
  - Kinsman, Bob.
  - Kirby, Patrick.
  - Klingberg, Frank J.
  - Klopper, Bruno.
  - Klutznick, Philip.
  - Knudsen, Vern O.
  - Koontz, Harold.
  - Koontz, Louis K.
  - Kostanick, Louis.
  - Koyama, Janice.
  - Koza, Michael P., b. 1951.
  - Krause, Anna.
  - Kremenliev, Boris A., b. 1911 May 23 - d. 1988 Apr 25
  - Krishnan, Radha.
  - Kunselman, Joan.
  - Kurrasch, Roy., 1946
  - Laczel, James.
  - Lamson, Baldwin G.
  - Lang, Fritz.
    Images from UCLA Extension Tribute Series featuring Fritz Lang, 1964.
  - Laskowski, Edward.
  - Laughlin, Helen Matthewson.
  - Lazier, Ed.
  - Lee, David R.
  - Lee, Robert Edward.
  - Lefschetz, Solomon.
  - Leonard, Frederick.
  - Leonard, Robert W.
  - Lepisto, Vic., 1966
  - Leppard, Henry.
  - Lewis, Benjamin G.
  - Lewis, F. Wesley.
  - Lie-gan, [ ? ].
  - Lierer, Paul.
  - Lobanov, Andre.
  - Lockie, Dave.
  - Lockman, Ron.
  - Lodge, Ardis.
  - Logan, Richard.
  - Longueil, Alfred E.
  - Longway, Harry J.
  - Love, J.
  - Lubetzky, Seymour., b.1898 April 28-d.2003
  - Luchs, George.
  - Lukather, Paul.
  - Lynn, Michael.
    UCLA men's basketball team member: 1965, 1966, 1968.
  - Lyon, Gretchen.
  - MacDonald, Gordon J.F.
  - MacInnis, James.